DANIEL THOMAS GIZZI DÍAZ

Profile

Email:

danielgizzidiaz@gmail.com

Phone

+56 9 85083952

My address

El Ligustro 1149, Rancagua, Chile

Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/daniel-thomas-gizzi-diaz/

SKILLS

Angular

Bootstrap

CSS3

Git HTMI

Javascript

Jauery

MySQL

SASS

NodeJS

MongoDB

Postman

Jira

Bitbucket

Figma

React

Tailwind CSS

Jest (Testing)

English (Intermediate)

ABOUT ME

I am an informatics engineer with 4 years of experience in the area of front-end developer using technologies like HTML, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, and Bootstrap 4 and 5. I am currently learning React. I have a good disposition, adaptability to the new environment, I am also very planned, and organizated person. I have great communication skills, and I accept criticism and feedback positively in order to learn and improve my professional career. I am also an empathic person and can stabilize good relationships.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

Multiplica (External employee for Entel), Santiago | 2022 - currently

My principal functions in the company are:

- Create components and responsive websites.
- Create code with good practices, reusable and clean.
- Resolve problems collaboratively with my team.
- Update content on a website for Entel.

The technologies utilized are: HTML5, CSS, SASS, Bootstrap (V4 & V5), JavaScript, Git, and Jira.

Web Developer

University of O'Higgins, Rancagua | 2019 - 2022

My principal functions in the company are:

- Update the contents on the University website, implement and add functionalities in an intranet.
- Implement structure for the all academic information.
- Development "Rich text editor" for the CMS in the Intranet.
- Generate and consume API's (external and internal).

The technologies utilized are: HTML5, CSS, RoR, Angular versión (4, 6, 8, 11), JQuery, Bootstrap (V3 & V4) and MySQL

EDUCATION

INACAP

2020 - 2021 | Informatic Engineering

INACAP

2017 - 2019 | Analyst Programmer